2pay4you.com 2016-10-18

# 2Pay4You | Virtual Wallet

  * 1 The following tenets regulate usage of your 2pay4you account as well as the usage of our services and any functions and technology offered by us. This includes without limitations, any information which you are offering through your usage of 2pay4you's services. In order to offer 2pay4you's services, 2pay4you requires certain personal information including your bank account data.  
Through agreeing to these tenets, you will agree to make your personal data available for usage in the following way. The protection of your data is first priority for 2pay4you, that's why we treat your data in compliance with the principles.  
Here it is described how the information will be used. Protection of your data is 2pay4you's highest priority, which is why your data will only be used in adherence to all aforementioned tenets. We will not issue any information to third parties. The information will solely be used to improve the quality of the services we offer. Under certain circumstances, we may pass on certain information to third parties under strict observance to all tenets.  
Please read our tenets carefully, as they apply to all 2pay4you services. By agreeing to these tenets, you will accept the usage and disclosure of your personal data in the aforementioned way. Please avoid registration and usage of 2pay4you's services if you in any way disagree with the tenets.  

####  **Notification of changes**

2 These tenets may be altered over the course of time, if for instance new functions are added to 2pay4you's services or customer suggestions are being applied. We will reserve the right to change these tenets at any given time or to publicize updated versions of it on our website. The updated version will apply as soon as it is published on our website. Some sections of 2pay4you's website may contain links to websites of third party providers. These websites are subject to separate tenets. 2pay4you is not responsible for their operation. Users who send data to third party websites should check relevant privacy policies before allowing their information to be processed.   
We herewith declare that these tenets do not constitute any sort of framework contract with regards to the European Union's payment service guideline (2007/64/EG).

#### **Minimum age requirement**

3 Please understand that children or minors below the age of 18 years may not transmit personal data or use 2pay4you's services.

#### **Required information**

4 2pay4you requires your name, address, telephone number and email address for you to be able to open an account or use its services. Verification is processed after a copy of your passport and a utility bill pertaining to your private bank account is made available. Businesses are required to submit their trade registration. After this information has been submitted you are permitted to send or receive unlimited payments.   
If you will be sending or receiving unusually high amounts of transactions, 2pay4you may require additional information regarding yourself or your business. This is to comply with regulations pertaining to money laundering.

#### **Third party access to personal data**

5 in order to protect our customers from fraud, all your data with regards to payment processing services will be checked. During such verification we will receive personal data about you from these providers.

#### **Customer Service Correspondence**

6 We will maintain records of your email and fax correspondence with customer service. We will additionally keep record of all of your customer service correspondence as well as all other correspondence addressed to you via 2pay4you.

#### **Disclosure to third parties to the exclusion of 2pay4you customers**

7 2pay4you will not sell or rent any personal data to third parties pertaining to marketing purposes without your prior agreement. Any disclosure will occur in strictly limited form and pertain to all tenets outlined within this document.
